Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Okay. mind your fingers.
It's late before now.
What are you looking at?
What are we going to do today?
Make yourself useful.
And give it some thought.
And a bottle of syrup.
Checkmate.
Leave the crate and come straight back.
The weather looks like it's picking up.
Don't come up here again.
Most people just say thank you.
It's very important that you listen.
Don't ever come up here again.
You know. me and my uncle come up here week after week bringing you supplies.
And yet you've never even come down to greet us.
Why is that?
Gale force winds are in serious effect across the coast.
Jessie. come on!
New storm formed. now heading towards the Hebrides.
Don't give me that look.
Jessie!
Come on!
Where's my uncle?
He's dead.
The trawler went down.
He was trapped.
We need to get this swelling down.
Why haven't you called anyone about what happened?
Not even the police?
Who else knows we're here?
No one?
Just rest.
You have to take me back.
You can't just keep me here.
I mean. I don't even understand why you're here.
My uncle told me that this lighthouse hasn't been working in years. yet you never leave here.
Why?
My family will be looking for me.
You don't have a family.
Mother died a few years back.
Never knew your father.
Your uncle's taken care of you ever since.
Because there was no one else.
How do you know that?
Well. someone will come looking.
Will they?
There's nothing here for anyone.
I know you're scared.
And you feel a lot of pain.
When you use a weapon.
You never loose your point. Your eyes on it.
Always balance your emotions.
Keep your wits.
Hold it like this.
Your thumb up against the hilt.
Tight in the palm.
Hold it up.
Good.
That's a strong one.
I'm gonna look at your ankle.
How did you know my uncle?
We served together.
In the Royal Marines.
He never told me your name.
What is it?
It wouldn't make a difference if he knew it.
I'd at least know what to call you.
We're doing okay so far.
Well. at least tell me your dog's name then.
He doesn't have one.
What?
That's crazy.
Your dog doesn't even have a name.
Well. I'm going to call him...
Jack.
Right. Jack?
Come.
Hey.
He likes to name Jack.
Jack.
Black Queen to F2.
You didn't tell me you could play chess.
You never asked.
Looks like I got myself a worthy opponent.
It's infected.
Can't we just go to a hospital?
No.
I'll get what's needed.
Thanks.
Ten years ago. the Prime Minister assured this committee and the nation
that her government. I quote. was not and would not ever collect data on British citizens.
And yet. thanks to the recent hack into MI6's servers.
we have now learned that not only has MI6 been systematically harvesting the personal information.
calls. emails and voting patterns of the British population.
but has been doing so in order to create an intelligence super system.
An advanced surveillance network called Total Human Engagement Analytics.
Or more affectionately. THEA.
Some of the details are. of course. classified.
The essence of THEA is to make better informed decisions. to anticipate threats more effectively.
What you've been doing is unlawfully invading the life of every person in this country.
If they're innocent. they have nothing to hide.
Since THEA went online. MI6 have intercepted threats at a rate never before imagined.
Perhaps you could simply say thank you.
Let me be clear on how this ends.
With you and Prime Minister Fordham under investigation and THEA dismantled.
Panorant was grandstanding. Prime Minister.
We both know the whole thing's a circus. just without the entertainment value.
Panorant is gaining traction in this election.
And this leak. it's a national embarrassment.
We're going to have to steady the ship.
You need a sacrificial lamb.
Let's face it. Stephen.
You're probably the best spymaster this country has ever produced.
But you are a hopeless bastard.
We all have our shortcomings. Prime Minister.
The tape's stopped.
It's just the two of us now.
I think this could be a blessing.
Really?
To get you back into the shadows where you belong.
It could be our little secret.
Indeed. Mum.
Roberta Frost. you're number two.
She'll take over as head of MI6 as an interim appointment.
And then after the election appoint somebody more appropriate.
Roberta's a good choice.
She's a good team player and we don't want any outsiders.
Exactly.
Enjoy your retirement.
Thank you. Prime Minister.
How old is she?
I said we were supposed to go in the first place but I thought we would go bowling instead.
It's a bit more fun though.
We always go to the sun.
I said we were supposed to go in the first place but I thought we would go bowling instead.
It's a bit more fun though.
High priority theatre.
We have a retinal match.
Timur Chemoev is a high value target wanted for the bombing of our embassy in Algeria.
His file is filled with similar atrocities.
Location?
Stornoway. Outer Hebrides. Scotland.
Repositioning satellites now.
Who's our nearest assault team?
Alpha.
Send them.
Did the medicine do its work?
I should be as good as new.
Thank you for the sweets. by the way.
I got these.
I hope they're okay.
It's the best I could do.
I like them.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Smells good.
So much better than porridge.
That. young lady. is a matter of opinion.
What?
What's happening?
Get in the bathroom.
Lock the door.
Don't make a sound.
Don't come out until I come for you.
Do it. Jesse.
Stay.
Weapons free.
Kill target on sight.
Find this fucker.
Out.
Spread out.
Box him in.
Yeah.
I found a girl.
Extracting her now.
Jack!
Ah!
Who is that?
Who are these guys?
Who you here for?
I need you to wait here.
Nothing's gonna happen.
I'm coming right back.
Where are you going?
Sorry. old boy.
I'm off to a reservation.
With baggage.
Okay. I'll be there.
It's time to leave.
But what about Jack?
Come on.
What about him?
What?
Jack!
Come on. we need to leave.
Alpha team. come in.
They're all gone.
Who the hell is this guy?
Whoever he is. he's not Chamoya.
Who's our nearest tier one asset?
Workman.
Activate him.
And notify all QRF teams in the region to be on standby.
Find out who that girl is.
Hey. come on!
You're hurt.
I'm fine.
But you're bleeding!
Come on.
Stay behind me.
I need to check something.
While you're here.
I need to go inside.
Get the keys.
You mean steal them?
Hey.
I need you to wait here.
Ever use a gun?
I shot squirrels with my uncle's air rifle.
Good enough.
Hold this.
One hand there.
And one there.
Hold it tight against your body.
Keep the barrel pointed to the dirt.
Keep your finger off the trigger.
It's sensitive.
Get your back against the fence.
That's as far as you go.
Put it down.
Please.
Whoa.
Let's...
Let's go slow.
Hey?
He's hurt.
Can you help him?
What am I looking at?
Timur Chermoev.
His profile's been altered.
See here?
The code's been manipulated to hide someone else.
So when a camera captures the real person. it misidentifies him as Chermoev.
It's very sophisticated stuff.
Whoever did this used self-deleting code.
And that's that guy.
Michael Mason?
He's one of ours?
Yeah.
But there aren't many details.
He was orphaned.
Former SBS operator.
KIA 10 years ago.
Apparently not.
Why would someone want to frame one of our own to be targeted?
I don't know.
Whoa.
I just tried to access his mission logs from Paul. and I got this.
Okay. keep digging.
Oh.
The Opstrom just intercepted a 999 call from a farm in Scotland.
matching Mason and our girl.
Call the Opstrom.
Let them know I'm on my way.
We're all good. sir.
Thank you. Ross.
Our target is not who we thought.
His name is Michael Mason.
I want him caught and brought in for questioning.
Where's my asset?
Workman's on route.
Please. please. please.
Workman.
Good.
Fuck you. Mason.
I'm not sure how good this'll hold.
I've only stetched goats and sheep.
I'm sure it's good.
Thanks.
Get out of here.
I'm gonna need your truck.
Keys are by the front door.
Go grab them.
Start it up.
I don't want you to hurt them.
I'm not gonna hurt them.
Okay?
Where's your son?
Callum?
Did you just go do something?
I called the police.
Let's move.
Cal. sit there.
Don't move.
Local authorities are responding to a home invasion at the farm.
Well. tell them not to engage.
Hold a perimeter.
Do not engage.
I repeat. do not engage.
We have personnel on route.
Are they going to arrest you?
It's not the police I'm worried about.
Go. go. go. go. go. go. go.
Hey. hey. wait.
Don't open the door.
Find out where those shots came from.
I'm sorry.
We need to stay here.
Come on.
Ah!
Mark. drop the weapon down.
Drop the weapon.
Hey. police.
stop.
Drop the weapon.
Mark. to my record. we have multiple men down.
In the back.
Keep your head down.
We're on Mason.
Patch me through to Wegman.
He's turned off his comms.
What the fuck is going on?
Stay down and hold on.
Bravo 2-1. we need backup immediately.
What the fuck?
We're switching cars.
Let's go.
Sir. it's done!
Hello. Roberta.
You call him to rub salt in the wound?
Hardly. sir.
For what it's worth. I think the Prime Minister sacking you was a grave misstep.
Flattery will get you everywhere.
How can I help you?
Does the name Michael Mason ring any bells?
Where did you hear that name?
He took down a full assault team.
Alone.
What I'm about to say doesn't exist outside of this conversation.
Years ago. we ran an off-book programme of elite operatives called Black Kites.
Operatives untethered from MI6's oversight.
And Mason was one of them?
Yeah. he was one of the first.
He was a prodigy.
He became our gold standard.
Then what happened?
He was sent to eliminate a foreign intelligence officer.
Instead. he spared the target. falsified his report and then disappeared.
Why would he defy orders?
We think he was turned.
I'm sure for a king's ransom.
You need to understand something.
Mason isn't just an assassin.
He's a precision instrument.
There's no stopping him.
You need to throw everything you've got at him. Roberta.
Michael Mason. unfortunately. has become a cancer on all that we stand for.
Yes. sir.
Ready to put your tradecraft to the test.
Am I going to get fired for this?
Who knows?
I do.
I found the Black Kite files on a backup server.
Mason was helping an Iranian scientist defect after he gave us everything on their nuclear program.
Instead of protecting him. Mason was ordered to kill him for deniability.
Looks like he refused.
Good girl. Maddy.
Dammit. Roberta.
Some people just can't help themselves.
You OK?
You think I can't handle the truth about who you really are. but I can.
Well. do you have family somewhere?
No.
You never wanted one?
It complicates things.
I'd rather it be complicated with them. than have my mum back. my uncle too.
Now I have none.
I wish I could tell you life would always be fair. but you already know the truth to that.
No case should have to go through what you did.
Just don't ever let it break your spirit. no matter what.
Okay?
Here. at least you had Jack.
He was your family.
Pretty cute.
Okay. there's a camera up on the wall in front of us.
There's also one behind us.
Once you get out on my side. we head down and keep it forward.
So when did you find religion?
Today.
When a ghost caught me.
We have different interpretations of what baggage means.
Just saying.
Now that's the workshop.
I'm always building one thing or another.
Just be careful though. there's lots of tools about.
Jesse. why don't you go get a drink?
The kitchen's in the back.
If you want me to leave so you guys can talk. you can just say that.
Hey. hey.
It's okay.
Spirited girl.
Who is she?
What are you doing here?
Her uncle and I. we served together.
I need a way out for her.
And I'll start figuring out how they found me.
Don't tell me you've got sentiment when you're old age.
She's just a kid who was in the wrong place at the wrong time.
Christ. mate.
Meet Thea.
I helped build it before I left the circus.
The big question is. how the hell did they find you after I buried you?
Shit.
When it was time for you to disappear. I changed your identity to an oil worker in Aberdeen.
A nobody.
But someone figured it out and swapped it to this guy.
A high-value terrorist on the watch list.
Which you know carries an interagency kill order.
Man of war.
You really think he still wants you dead after all this time?
I broke the only rule that matters to him.
Fuck his rules.
You refused to kill an innocent man that you promised to help after he helped us.
Can you shut it down?
Not from here.
I mean. it wouldn't matter anyway.
You've been ID'd.
All those years on that line.
You're supposed to stay dead. Macy.
Yeah. that's what I thought.
I just need you to keep Jessie safe.
Man of war knows who she is now.
But she makes for a loose end.
You care about her. don't you?
This is where we part ways.
Can you keep her here?
Look. Macy. I can't.
Why?
He has cancer.
And my mum took the same meds for her.
I'm sorry I'm such a drag to you.
Hey. Jessie. wait.
Is she right?
Dr said I might get one more Christmas.
Oh. Jesus.
I'd help you if I could.
But you know I can't be responsible for her.
My hands are tied.
What if I go to Kamal?
He has the means to get her out.
Undetected.
Kamal Shah?
No.
No. no. no way.
Not an option.
Hey. look. he's the best at what he does.
Yeah. because he's a violent trafficker.
And you haven't got MI6 behind you to control him now.
Let me worry about that.
Just help me get to him.
Can you do that?
Listen. I can tell you when to turn left or right.
That's about it.
Good enough.
Jessie. it's time to go.
Hey. Jessie. come on.
Were you really going to leave me here?
I'm sorry.
Your safety is the most important thing to me.
Please.
Fine.
Don't stand by the wall.
I didn't.
Just do it.
Stand by the wall.
Let him go.
Just let him go.
Get in and go!
Go. go. get in!
Who was that?
Him.
20 years ago.
Ross!
We're doubling down.
Get your team ready.
Yes. sir.
The Wi-Fi in there will suffice for my needs.
Here. take my hand coat.
Help you hide those good looks.
Right.
Use only for an emergency. or you know they'll trace you in a heartbeat.
Yeah. we're gonna have to switch motors.
They know we're in this one now.
You take care. young lady.
Thank you.
I wish you'd kill that man.
I know it's wrong to say that. but...
maybe I'm becoming like you.
You're nothing like me. Jessie.
And I'm keeping it that way.
But how do you know?
Because I've seen who you really are.
Look. by tonight. all of this will be behind you.
You'll start a brand new life.
Somewhere normal. somewhere safe.
Alone.
What will you do?
You can't go back to your island.
There's always another island.
I could come with you.
You don't want this life.
Always on the run. looking over your shoulder.
And you do?
Hey. Jessie. you need to understand.
The only way that I can protect you is to stop the people that are doing this.
You need to stay close to me. all right?
Any sign of Mason?
No.
We have nothing.
He knows what he's doing.
You're right.
I found an unknown login to Thea from outside MI6.
I have a bad feeling.
Can you I.D.? No.
There is...
There is something I can try.
Whatever it is. do it quickly.
There's a camera.
It'll see us.
Let's hope it's working.
Sorry. mate.
Invite only.
Take me to Kamal.
I'll break your other wrist.
Well played. Roberta.
My trap worked.
I got him.
It's...
Oh. shit.
That's...
Stephen Manafort.
I know.
We'll do it with him later.
Get me every camera in this club now.
Let's keep this walk nice and smooth.
Tell him it's Michael Mason.
Do you know Michael Mason. boss?
Michael Mason.
Look at you.
No country. no badge.
Just a poor bastard who thought he had friends in the game.
Who's she?
I need a way out.
Of the country.
For her.
Tonight.
New identity.
Somewhere off-grid.
No.
No?
How do you think you've been allowed to operate for all these years. Kamal?
With impunity.
And with the luxury of getting rid of your competition.
At the same time. by ratting them out to Manafort and I.
Manafort's gone.
Not gone.
Unshackled.
He's more dangerous than ever.
To us both.
You're lying.
Am I?
The second the security camera outside saw me walk in here to your club.
every operative that MI6 has within 25 miles was activated to bring me in.
I already got ten minutes. Tubbs.
All I need is for you to get her out. and I'll go cut the head off the snake.
Bury all our dirty little secrets with him.
Wait here.
Please come with me.
You heard the deal I made with him.
I need to honour my side.
Honour your side?
I think you want to die.
What's that supposed to mean?
You don't think you have anything to live for.
If you really wanted to. you'd come.
Hey. people like me don't get to go and live a normal life.
You keep telling yourself that.
Hey. you're stronger than this.
No. I'm not.
Yes. you are.
I need you to be.
Just promise me you're not going to die.
Exactly.
Right. where's my tactical team?
En route.
I want Mason and the girl taken in alive.
They are not to open fire.
Car's out front.
How far around is your team?
They're still en route. sir.
Where the fuck are you?
30 seconds out. sir.
The girl is at Achilles' heel.
Use that to your advantage.
Copy that. sir.
Passport. ID. and 20.000 euros.
She goes to our safe house in Spain for now.
Boat leaves Isle of Dogs in 30 minutes.
It won't wait.
Just make sure you finish what you started.
You handle your end.
I'll handle mine.
Wait. on the other side of the square.
Let's move.
Let's go.
This is Zulu.
Two minutes out.
Do we have an exact location inside?
Wait. you're not already there.
That's a negative.
Matter of order.
Tell them that there's a rogue team already inside.
They need to get in there now.
Now!
Let me go!
Arthur!
Matterport's guards have got Jessie.
Found her.
Hold on.
Right out the front entrance.
Cut across the square and turn south.
She's being carried towards a black transit van.
I've got her!
Move. move!
Go. go. go!
Get ready!
He's gonna be coming for her!
Get in there!
I don't see Mason.
There!
Mason's heading right towards you.
Move!
I got you. it's okay.
I got you. I got you. Jesse. I got you.
You okay?
Time to go.
She's all right.
You're going to be okay.
Come on.
I'm going to lower her down.
You better hurry.
Ready?
Jesse. it's time to go.
No.
Bo won't wait.
No. no. no.
You said you can't live a normal life for your own.
You just have to come on the boat with me.
And we can disappear and we can have a normal life.
Come on.
Please. no. please. please.
You're my hub now.
I don't want to leave you.
Hey. Jesse.
No.
Listen to me.
Jesse. this is the only way I can keep you safe.
I'm sorry.
No. I'm not leaving without you.
I have to save you.
You've saved me already.
Come on.
Now. Jesse.
No.
Jesse's safe.
Do you even know why you're doing this?
Does it matter?
You can't save her either.
get in there.
You are my dearest.
my greatest weapon.
And then you broke the rules.
Black kites know one law above all.
Loyalty.
You put your conscience first and the mission second.
I finally put humanity over blind obedience.
Oh. yeah. there it is.
The righteous martyr.
And a foolish one.
You allowed a civilian into this game.
A child.
What good is all that humanity with her blood on your hands?
That's not gonna happen.
And you know it.
I don't want that either.
You really think you can outrun what you are?
We are who we are. Mason.
I have been given complete autonomy to make black kites stronger than ever.
I want you with me. by my side. as we were.
You're the very reason I didn't pull the trigger ten years ago.
And why I have to now.
What's up?
Anything new?
Just having some cocoa and reading a book.
Zoom in and up. Rez.
And maybe we should start exploring other ways to find him.
He hid from us for ten years.
Until her.
It's a matter of when.
Wait.
It's him.
Your friend said this was for you.
Where is he?
He was there a moment ago.
Subtitles By William Bender
Contact : williambndr2024@gmail.com
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm